(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-21T00:33:41.513370",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hello everybody.
Welcome to my 3D debut!
Oh god, what year is it?
Where am I? Well, we're here in my office.
Hello, everyone!
Hi!
So today we have some exciting stuff happening,
but don't you guys want to see my desk and my office? Isn't that nice? Look. Wow.
Got all these papers here.
Shall we do a spin?
We're watching the pre-chat and you guys are being so cute.
And thank you for coming.
Oh, Konichiwatsan, everyone! Arigatou!
Um, I'm gonna try to put my feet up on this desk. Let's see if it works.
And I want to get some cool screenshots. Make sure you guys take a picture, you can post on Twitter with this hashtag.
Yeah. Kick back, relax, you know, just thinking around.
Maybe I'll just take a nap.
I've been working so hard for this, for today's showcase and now I just want to take a break.
Oh, who's this? There's pupils here.
Oh, pictures! Let's see. Uh, who is first? Ina!
Ina's debut, so cute. I love her. She does this so well. I don't know how she does it.
And mine looks pretty cool, too, right?
And then we have, uh, Kiara. Kiara, wait, or Callie first?
No, it was Kiara first, yeah.
Uh, the worm.
Oh sorry, just reading chat.
Okay, yeah.
Uh, and then after was Callie and then Gura was yesterday.
Ah, their debuts were so fun to watch.
We have a collab happening tomorrow, too, so make sure to tune into that.
But first, don't you guys want to see my office? Yay!
I want to show you guys around my office.
Oh my god, it's like the first time reveal! You guys have never seen this before, right?
Whistle whistle.
Look at these nice kicks!
Cute, cute, cute! Pa, pa, pa!
Cool, right?
Ah, what are those?
So smooth!
What are you looking at?
Oh.
Oh, and my watch.
Ooh, time-traveled!
What year is it?
Okay.
Let's see.
Yeah, tada!
Finally, full high-quality official 3D, let's go!
All right, well, should I show you guys around over here?
Bubba!
Bubba, I made it all the way to Japan!
And Bubba's so cute!
And Bubba, pet the pet, pet, pet, pet.
And Bubba, Bubba.
Maybe Bubba knows some tricks.
Bubba!
Bubba can fly!
It's magic!
Bubba, how are you doing that? Maybe it's his cape, the cape's making him fly.
And Bubba, can you do... Bubba, do a flip!
Let's see if Bubba can do a flip.
Woo!
Oh, shit, I did a flip!
Now, if you guys ask for it, there it is, there's the flip!
Bubba, Bubba's so small, right?
I wonder if Bubba can sit down. Maybe Bubba can sit over here.
Bubba, use the chair! Bubba, use the chair!
Tada!
Bubba's a detective now. Wow, how cute!
And I want to see from the desk. Aw, cute, cute.
Okay, Bubba, Bubba, jump!
Tada!
And can Bubba dance? Bubba, dance!
Aw, Bubba, good boy! Good boy, Bubba!
So cute, right?
All right, Bubba, come on, this way.
I want to show you guys around my office a little bit.
Tada! This is a conspiracy board.
And I'm at the center of it all.
But this is this is a evil Ame, right?
But this is this is an evil Ame, right?
We don't look exactly the same, see?
That one's evil.
I'm the good Ame.
Uh-huh. Yes, yes, totally.
Right, Bubba, that that Ame is evil. Bubba, attack!
Connected to everything!
All right, over here, fish tank, fish tank!
Yeah, there's no fish in it, but it's pretty, right? Bubba ate all the fish. Bubba was hungry.
Um, there's no fish tank in there yet. They did not die. They were Bubba ate them. They're just sleeping.
Um, and then over here, the window! Ah, I love having a window in the back.
It's just a nice I mean, this one, I need to clean it a little bit.
I'm not going to lie.
It needs a little bit of a scrub.
And then we have the stars up here. Wow!
They're too high, I can't reach.
And then the monitor so I can look at chat. This is definitely where I'm looking at chat and not somewhere else in the room.
Yes, right here. Right here.
And of course, my mixing set.
And now, over here, whoa.
Sus.
These are the the ones on the desk were the good myth members, but these are the evil versions.
Sus. Sus. Sus. And just a little sus.
Oh, yeah. Well, we have some things uh you know to get to.
I'll show you a little bit more over here.
These are my boxes. I need to unpack.
And did you guys know that box is hako in Japanese? Doesn't it sound familiar like uh certain stuff.
Get a phone call.
I have a phone? Oh, yeah, I do have a phone.
Let me see. I wonder who it could be.
Moshi moshi.
Yagoo?
Yagoo's Yagoo's on the phone. He's calling me.
Hold on, let me sit.
Got to answer for this. Hi.
Naruhodo.
I see.
Oh.
Honto desu ka?
Is that true?
Okay, okay. Uh-huh, okay.
Really important uh phone call, item meeting.
Uh, actually, there's a case for us to go check out, a crime scene.
We've got a goal,
and see what the heck all that was about.
Let's go to detective work!
Get out!
Papa, come on.
Huh?
A crime scene right here, in the middle of the street?
I guess this is what Yago called me for.
We should take a really close look, examine all the clues, and try to figure out who might be behind this.
I guess the investigators came by and prepped this scene already for me.
We have the outline of a body here and one, two, three, four, four clues.
Okay.
Well, before I touch anything, my hands are clean, don't worry.
I'm going to take a picture. Let's take a picture. Hold on, let me get my camera.
All right, this is better before I infect everything with my germs and fingerprints.
Let's take a look, take a picture here.
Gun?
Now let's see here, a banana? What's this doing here?
Okay, let me just take one of the crime scene in total.
Tew tew tew tew...
And here we have what is this, a machete? A gun? I mean a knife?
Let's take a picture.
And lastly we have a hat. Baseball cap? Let's see. All right, let's take a picture.
Okay, I'm going to have to get closer now. Let me get my magnifying glass out of my pocket. All right.
First, let's have a look at this banana. This banana really caught my interest.
It looks unopened, uneaten banana. Let me take a look.
I don't see any bruises on it yet.
So maybe, maybe what happened is they were walking down the street and about to eat their banana when somebody attacked them.
All right, let me take a look at this hat. Baseball cap. Let's see. They were probably wearing this and it's pretty far from their head.
There's no blood on it, so let me take a closer look. Maybe somebody wanted their hat?
Maybe somebody was trying to steal their hat, I wonder, and tried taking it from them while they were eating a banana, about to eat a banana.
All right, let me take a look at this. I see... we have this machete. It doesn't look like there's any marks on it. Though they probably didn't even get to use this. I don't think that that's the murder weapon, but maybe, maybe it's a case of self-defense.
And last but not least, let's take a look at the gun, which I suspect to be the murder weapon. Let's see. Shiny? It's like a skin, very shiny skin on this. Pretty flashy looking gun.
Let me think. Well, maybe what happened was that they were walking down the street after just buying a fresh banana, and they were about to eat it when suddenly somebody attacked them and wanted their hat?
What do you guys think? Could it be? Maybe somebody was filming like a TikTok video or something? I mean, look at how their pose was... maybe no, that's probably like a "no, please!" But it kind of looks like they're doing a, you know...
What do you guys think? Could it be? Maybe somebody was filming like a TikTok video or something? I mean, look at how their pose was... no, that's probably like a "don't, please!" But it kind of looks like they're doing a, you know...
I think I... I missed one.
There's something over here.
Hold on, I need to get a closer look.
I'll show you guys.
Whoa.
I have the view.
Footsteps?
Hold on.
Let me get this for archive purposes,
whole scene.
Their legs are spread so wide!
What happened?
Okay.
Now, let's take a closer look here.
Footsteps?
Hmm, these are way smaller than my feet.
Super small footsteps.
Wait, small footsteps?
Hmm.
I wonder.
Let's think this through.
Small footsteps, banana,
a hat that somebody wanted,
a shiny gun?
Wait a second.
Why is this ringing bells?
Could it be?
Wait, what is that?
I hear... I hear something from up there.
Huh?
What? What is that?
You dare enter my dimension?
This field ain't big enough for the two of us.
Especially with your fat ass!
Ah!
Not this again!
Small Ame, I could tell
it was you from these clues!
Appearing at the crime scene
just confirms it!
Small Ame, I'm putting you under citizen's arrest!
You fell right for my trap!
What's this?!
Keep missing, it's pain!
I got hit!
Don't worry, guys. These are tranquilizer darts, not real bullets.
Usually I would take you back to the office for holding until police arrive, but I have guests coming over.
Here. This should do the trick.
And... one.
Next...
two.
And Small Ame, you're next.
Hiya!
And don't come back!
I think we should head back to the office and celebrate. Let's go!
Yay, we did it! Case closed!
Small Ame be dead. I'm sure she'll be back, she's like a cockroach.
I can't get rid of her.
Uh, well, now that we're here, back at the office, I am expecting guests, like I said.
So, uh, maybe we should celebrate first, how about that?
And then we'll have some guests maybe.
Uh, I do have a treat for you guys for being such good investigators.
Ta-da!
Oh, this thing is heavy!
Look at this. Ta-da!
Whoa.
There's a lot of liquid in here, huh? At least two gallons.
'Cause there's so many of you guys in chat, we got to, you know,
get an appropriate amount to make sure it's effective, that is.
Isn't it cool? It's like a rocket launcher, like...
I like it. All right, well,
you guys ready for your dose?
Wait, before we do this, do you guys have any dance requests for me?
'Cause we're going to have a little dance.
A dance-off, sort of.
I want to know if you guys have any dances that you want to see first before I give you this...
injection.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
The worm?
All right, all right. Maybe we'll do a worm, maybe. Flossing?
Flossing, really? Okay, you know what, that's it. Stop!
Hey, can you feel the effects yet? Huh?
Hey, do you guys recognize this song?
All right, you guys asked for a floss, right?
I can I still can't floss. Shit!
If you guys recognize this song, you're a real one.
A real one.
And the worm.
Okay, I'll do a worm like this. How about this?
Okay. Oh, a short worm. Short worm.
Whoa. That doesn't really work with this trio of me.
All right, stop out of it. We got guests coming. Come on.
Hey, did that help you guys snap out of it?
Come on. Come on.
We have a guest now.
One guest.
But for right now, let's see.
Who could it be?
Any Any guesses?
No?
Maybe?
No, maybe?
Ah!
Hello, konkanpa!
Eh, my name is Genius Panko, yá yozora meru.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you very much for having me here.
I'm so happy you're here.
Today, we're going to play a game.
Yeah, with a ball.
What game do you think?
Maybe baseball?
Home run! No, we're not playing baseball.
Maybe soccer? Soccer? Should we play soccer?
Okay. Well, why don't we go see...
Shall we?
Okay, we'll kick.
Ready? Ready? Set, no, go!
What is this? What is this?
It's Hopscotch!
Ken-ken-pa! Ken-ken-pa!
Yeah! We're going to play hopscotch...
And e, English name is hopscotch.
But in Japanese it's called ken-ken-pa.
And every time you jump on one, you do ken-ken-pa, ken-ken-pa, ken-ken-pa.
So I'll explain the rule to you guys, but, uh, yeah.
So this is how it works.
So you throw the ball, and whichever square it lands on, you get the points for that square. So we're going to try to throw it on like a high number, but also...
Uh we only have five turns. So whoever wins at the end of five turns that has the most points, we'll get a prize. Victory prize!
ことです。
That's it.
イエーイ。
Yay.
そして、合計点数が多かったほうが
And whoever has the highest total score
勝ち！
wins!
ケンケンパを失敗したり、得点のマスからボールがはみ出したりしたら、
If you mess up the hopscotch, or if the ball goes out of the scoring box,
失敗！
you fail!
はい、点は加算されない、ということだね。
Right, so no points are added, got it?
イエーイ、落としせーん。
Yay, watch your step.
So because Mel is my senpai, Mel gets the first turn! Yeah!
しょうがないな。
Oh well.
私のポンパイヤの力、見せてやろう。
I'll show you the power of my "pompai"!
では、第1球。
Now, ball one.
いきます！
Here I go!
魔力が…… 魔力が……
My magic power... My magic power...
くっ！
Ugh!
The rules are if you get it out, it goes to the next person's turn. So I guess it's my turn!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
Hehehe. Next! Okay. Next step!
頑張れ！Gamer, let's go.
You got this! Gamer, let's go.
10 points! Okay, now let's see her real test. No switching feet!
ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン……
Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop...
ボールを……ゲット！いや……おー！
Get the ball... Got it! No... Oh!
あと帰るだけだよ。
Just gotta go back now.
ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、パ！
Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, jump!
イェーイ！ First point for Ame!
Yay! First point for Ame!
はい、メルのターン！
Okay, Mel's turn!
寝ても10ポイント。がんばって！
Even sleeping is 10 points. Do your best!
おっ！おっ！ナイス！8！よし、いきます。
Oh! Oh! Nice! 8! Alright, here I go.
ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、パ！
Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, jump!
うわっ！おー、ナイス！やるじゃん、ジャンプオーバー！
Whoa! Oh, nice! You jumped over it!
……からのこれ広い！
...And pick it up! Nice, nice!
ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、パ、ゴール！ナイス、よっしゃ！
Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, jump, goal! Nice, yes!
Good job! Good job! Okay. Ame, turn number two!
セブンポイント、オッケー。
Seven points, okay.
ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、パ！後ろって……。
Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, jump! Behind...
オッケー、ナイス！メルのターン、ナンバー3！
Okay, nice! Mel's turn, number 3!
負けられない。
I can't lose.
ボーリング。に、あっ、おっ、あっ、あー！ナイス、オッケー、セブンポイント！
Bowling. Two, ah, oh, ah, ah! Nice, okay, seven points!
ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、パ！うわ、うわっ！
Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, jump! Whoa, whoa!
ナイス、ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、ゴール！ナイス、ゴール！どうや！どうや！
Nice! Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, goal! Nice, goal! How's that? How's that?
Next. オッケー、next step. オッケー、no problem.
Next. Okay, next step. Okay, no problem.
1、2、3！あ！アウト？あ、アウト？アウト！アウト、うわ！shit！
1, 2, 3! Ah! Out? Ah, out? Out! Out, whoa! Shit!
メイン、いっ、あたし、アウト、それは、えーと。
Wait, I think it's out. It's on like, on the line, right on the line. What do you guys think? Chat, you guys said out?
Chat says out.
どっちだ？あ、Definitely out.
Which is it? Ah, definitely out.
Out.
あれ、おや？ That's definitely out.
Mel's out, right? Out?
Yeah.
うーん、yeah.
Mhm, yeah.
オッケー、Mel turn! Number four!
Okay, Mel's turn, number four!
You guys are supposed to be on my side. Chat, come on.
テンザテン、テンポイント。
10 to 10, 10 points.
ゴーゴー！うーん！あ、オッケー！セブンセブン！
Go, go! Ugh! Ah, okay! Seven, seven!
ラッキーセブン。ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、広い！
Lucky seven. Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, pick it up!
ケン、ケン、パ！ケン、ケン、ケン、ケン、やった！おー、ナイス、イエーイ！
Hop, hop, jump! Hop, hop, hop, hop, yay! Oh, nice, yay!
ラスキュート、キュート！オッケー。
Last cute, cute! Okay.
Ame turn number four. Nine, nine.
Ame's turn number four. Nine, nine.
あ！あ！あ！あ！あ！あ！しゃ！おかしい！
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! Shoot! That's weird!
Maybe I'll get a 10 on the next one. Is anybody keep- chat, you guys keeping track of the points?
Maybe I'll get a 10 on the next one. Is anybody keeping track of the points, chat?
これは……アウト？アウト！アウト、アウト！ Like referee.
Is this... out? Out! Out, out! Like a referee.
オッケー！
Okay!
ラスト、ラスターン！いきます！がんばって！
Last, last turn! Here I go! Do your best!
うっ！うわっ！おっ！おっ！
Ugh! Whoa! Oh! Oh!
Six! Oh, six spot. Okay.
ファイト
You got this!
せーの、けんけんぱ、けんけん、うっ
Ready, hop-hop-jump, hop-hop, whoops!
ゲット！
Got it!
ナイス
Nice!
けんけんぱ、けんけん、ぱー
Hop-hop-jump, hop-hop, jump!
やったー
Yay!
おっけー、あめ、ラスト！
Okay, Ame, last turn!
あめのらすと？
Ame's last turn?
Maybe if I blow on the ball, right?
よっ、ふう～
Here we go... whew!
え？いん？
Eh? In?
え、え、いん、いん？
Eh, eh, in, in?
いん、おっけー、おっけー
In, okay, okay.
えすぽい、いんだよ、guys
It's spot-in, guys!
おっけー
Okay!
けんけんぱ、けんけんぱ、けんけん
Hop-hop-jump, hop-hop-jump, hop-hop...
おっ！あ、あっ、あっ、うわあ！
Whoa! Ah, ah, ah, whoa!
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
いたた
Ouch...
おめでとう
Congratulations!
おめでとう？
Congratulations?
I think I lost. I have really bad luck.
わあ
Wow!
まさか勝てる？勝っちゃったの？
No way, did I win? Did I actually win?
Victory!
勝者はわ、やったー！
The winner is... Yay!
ウィナー！
Winner!
コロンビア、おー、ナイス
Colombia, oh, nice!
天才、天才！
Genius, genius!
Well, your prize.
Victory present.
これ勝ったらどうなるんですか？
What happens if I win this?
ああ、here, for you.
Ah, here, for you.
ただいま、自撮りカメラを、ゲットしたぞー！
Tadaima! I got the selfie camera!
She has control of the selfie camera.
イエイ、アメリア、イエイ！
Yay, Amelia, yay!
Mel, do you have pose requests?
ピクチャーリクエスト for Ame.
Picture request for Ame.
アメちゃん、アメちゃんだよ。
Ame-chan, it's Ame-chan!
アメル、アメル。
Amel, Amel.
なんか、ポーズ、ポーズ取る？
Should we, like, strike a pose?
うん、ポーズ。えー、キャット？
Yeah, poses. Uh, cat?
キャットポーズ。キャット？
Cat pose. Cat?
にゃにゃ、にゃー
Nya nya, nyaaa!
あ、カット？おっ？
Ah, cut? Oh?
何々これ？え？え？え？
What, what is this? Eh? Eh? Eh?
カット？あ、カット、ねこみみ？
Cut? Ah, cut, cat ears?
にゃーん！
Nyaaa!
にゃー、そうきゅーち！
Nyaaa, so cute! So cute!
Ame, hi.
My girlfriend.
Best friend.
じゃ、Ame、change？
So, Ame, change?
My turn.
うわ、すみません。
Whoa, sorry!
ソリー、ソリー。
Sorry, sorry.
おっ、バカ、バカ、バカ！
Oh, baka, baka, baka!
パンチ、パンチ、パンチ、パンチ！
Punch, punch, punch, punch!
キック、キック！
Kick, kick!
ばか、ばか！キッキング、オッケー！
Baka, baka! Kッキング, okay!
え、maybe Mel pose?
Uh, maybe Mel's pose?
ポーズ、何取る？
Pose, what should I take?
えー、うーん、あ、うーん、あ、キス？
Uh, hmm, oh, hmm, oh, kiss?
あ、ちゅー？
Ah, chu?
あ、ちゅ！
Ah, chu!
あー、So cute!
Ah, so cute!
Maybe chat has a pose.
Do you guys want something from us?
Maybe a a say so pose?
Maybe a Say So pose?
Say so pose? Say so pose?
Say so pose.
え？T pose？No, no T pose.
Eh? T-pose? No, no T-pose.
なに、なに？
What, what?
T pose？
T-pose?
T poseなの？
猫耳？
Cat ears?
え、で、え、Hold hand？
Eh, and, uh, hold hand?
お、おっけー。
Ah, okay.
あ、I'm grabbing something else.
Ah, I'm grabbing something else.
たこ？
Tako?
はい、はい。
Hai, hai.
あ、heart？
Ah, heart?
ハート？
Heart?
あ、ハート。ハート、ハート。おっけー。ハート？
Ah, heart. Heart, heart. Okay. Heart?
ハート？うーん、難しい、難しいね。
Heart? Hmm, difficult, it's difficult, huh?
オーケー、オールライト。楽しい。
Okay, alright. Fun!
オーケー。
Okay.
あ、We're taking getting rid of getting rid of the selfie camera.
Ah, we're taking—getting rid of the selfie camera.
あ、こっち？
Ah, this way?
あ、これ？
This?
オーケー、we'll try again. ハート！
Okay, we'll try again. Heart!
なふなふ？
Nafu nafu?
ラブラブ？
Love-love?
あめ。
Ame.
Alright. Ah, Mel, do you know how to floss? forallす？
Alright. Ah, Mel, do you know how to floss? Floss?
like this. And this.
や、や！
Ya, ya!
ナイス！
Nice!
オーライツ。
Alright.
Well.
あ。
Ah.
ありがとう。
Arigatou.
あ、thank you for coming.
Ah, thank you for coming.
あ、みんな呼んでくれて、ありがとう、サンキュー。
Ah, thank you everyone for inviting us. Thank you.
ありがとう。
Arigatou.
I'm happy.
Me too!
イエイ！
Yay!
楽しい！
So fun!
楽しかった！
That was fun!
みんなもありがとう！
Thank you everyone, too!
あ、thank you everyone.
Ah, thank you everyone.
バイバ～イ！
Bye-bye!
大好き！
Love you!
I love you, Amelia.
あー、すき！
Ah, love you!
またね、みんな、ありがとうございました。
See you all again, thank you so much.
Bye bye! Mwah!
Bye-bye! Mwah!
That show was for me, not for you guys. Hey, don't get too excited.
We kind of lost it, didn't we? We got it. We got it pretty good.
We kind of lost it, didn't we? We got it pretty good.
Ah, that was Mel.
夜空メル、she's so cute.
Yozora Mel, she's so cute.
And she has really good songs, go listen to them!
Yeah, thank you. All right.
We do have some more guest. Well, any guesses?
We do have some more guests. Well, any guesses?
Any guesses maybe? Maybe could it be some of the people that were in the chat
earlier? I saw the pre-chat.
All right, let's say hello to our guest. Calling in. Moshimoshi!
All right, let's say hello to our guests. Calling in! Moshimoshi!
Hello, hello!
Oh! Who is that?
They sound cute!
Hello! Hello! Cute!
Thank you guys for calling in.
Hey, do you guys want to do some thank you?
Hey, do you guys want to do some— thank you!
Why don't we do self-introductions starting over here? Who's this crazy looking one?
Why don't we do self-introductions starting over here? Who's this crazy-looking one?
Well, hello. I'm Crazy Ollie from Hollive Indonesia Second Generation. Again, congrats!
Well, hello! I'm Kureiji Ollie from Hololive Indonesia Second Generation. Again, congrats!
Ah, thank you so much. Thank you.
Okay, over here, who's this with the squishies?
Oh, oh. Oh, hi! It's Nashi Mumeme from Hololive English Council. Congrats, Ame!
Oh, hi! It's Nanashi Mumei from Hololive English Council. Congrats, Ame!
Ah, thank you! Thank you, thank you.
And over here we have, who's this cat? Nicola Petatpetat.
And over here we have, who's this cat? Nikola Petatpetat.
Hello, I am Zeta, Secret Agent from the future corp.
Excuse me. Hello, I am Zeta, Secret Agent from the Future Corp.
From the future?
Ah, thank you. You know where Amelia's in my front from the future?
Ah, thank you. You know where Amelia's in my friend from the future?
I guess, yeah, she's from the future. I didn't know that. Huh. I guess that's that's probably why. Ah, that's why we know each other. I see.
I guess, yeah, she's from the future. I didn't know that. Huh. I guess that's probably why. Ah, that's why we know each other. I see.
All right, well, we're here to play game, a game of Charades.
All right, well, we're here to play a game, a game of Charades.
Yeah, you guys should know how Charades works, but I'll explain it anyways.
Charades, I'm going to act out like, you know, an action, or a person, or an item, or like an animal, and then you guys have to guess and then at the end you guys get a prize if you guess correctly.
Charades, I'm going to act out like, you know, an action, a person, an item, or an animal, and then you guys have to guess...
A prize? I want a prize. Your presence is already a present.
Seriously, thank you for calling in.
Okay, well, shall we get started? Are you guys ready?
Yes, yes, yes, for sure.
Okay, we'll do the first one then. All right, first, no talking. Sorry, that's the rules of Charades.
Okay, we'll do the first one then. All right, first off, no talking. Sorry, that's the rules of Charades.
I can make noises though.
Please do. Wait, what is she doing? What? What is she doing? She's sitting in a car?
What? Is she driving? She's driving! Elevator driver? Taxi driver? Bus driver? Truck driver?
Oh, race car driver? Oh, yeah! That was it, it was race car driver.
Said chat is like crank that.
Chat is like "crank that."
Yeah, I was trying to get out of the car, dude. You know how they go like they're really fast? Like they screw in the new tires and stuff.
Yeah, I was trying to get out of the car, dude. You know how they go really fast? They screw in the new tires and stuff.
All right, well nice job, that was fast. You guys are smart.
All right, well nice job, that was fast. You guys are too smart.
That was so quick!
I'm surprised.
Well, we have a lot here still. Let's keep going.
Okay, next one. Okay, okay. This is kind of difficult. Okay.
Cute detective. She's handing out flyers.
She looks like she's doing up a Gundam stuff. I don't know what she's doing.
She looks like she's doing Opal Gundam stuff. I don't know what she's doing.
Destroying things maybe feeding the birds?
Oh, basketball? No.
Wait, are you opening a champagne bottle?
Wait, opening a wine bottle? No.
Popping a champagne? No, yes? She's nodding.
Confetti? No.
I think we're running out of time.
Is there a time limit? Oh no. Oh no, um she's making it rain, I don't know.
I just don't know. She got something. A bouquet?
I just don't know. She's got something. A bouquet?
You're throwing a bouquet? No.
She's she's doing something.
Alright, opening soda? Oh.
Alright, I think we're out of time.
Nice try. That was a hard one.
That was really hard.
It was cork.
Cork! Oh!
Cork, yeah.
It was just a cork!
Yeah! Oh, I thought it was champagne bottle.
I- I see.
I see.
Got to up the level.
You guys were there. You were so close.
You guys were nodding! I see.
It was just a cork, yeah. So...
Yeah, yeah. The chat got it.
I was surprised actually. Thank you, chat.
That's hard! You did a good job!
Oh, thank you.
Let's go for the next one.
I'm a mute.
Jellyfish?
Yeah, that's it! That was really fast!
It was jellyfish! And then I was trying...
You guys are good! All right, next...
You just really looked like one.
Yeah, it's I think it's the cape. I- I like how it looks.
It's also my tassels.
Oh, yeah. Now you look like a real jellyfish.
And we were- when we were doing this, we figured out it looks kind of weird.
Oh, one second, my thingy fell out.
Okay.
All right, next one.
Let's do the next one. I think I'm ready.
Yeah.
Okay.
Here we go.
A shopping cart?
No.
She's sweeping? She's sweeping?
Janitor?
Yeah! Yeah, it was janitor!
What? Are these too easy?
No, you're just really good! Leave some for us!
We're on the same brainwave.
I'm a sweep.
All right, we still have a lot more.
Okay, all right.
Ready for the next one?
Yeah, this one's going to be hard.
Okay, ready. Got to get this one.
Here we go.
Oh, she's lying down. Oh, she's sitting.
That.
What? What?
She is inside- inside a box?
No. I- I think that counts.
Oh, okay. Does it count?
Oh, okay. It does, it does.
It was box!
Man, we're a couple of gamers, huh?
The gamer squad! Apex squad! Let's go!
Yeah, we are apex squad! Let's go!
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do!
I feel like this next one you guys will get really fast, too.
Okay.
All right.
I'm a mute.
Bunny?
Bunny girl!
A- a- a frog?
Oh, what are they called? What are they called?
The things that you hop on?
Pogo stick! Pogo stick!
Nice! Nice, nice!
All right, I think this will be the last one.
You guys are too good.
Oh.
All right.
We're gaming.
You're too good.
Let's see.
I'm a mute.
Takanashi Kiara!
You guys are so like that.
Yeah, yeah.
Nice! That was it! You guys won!
Wait, you got all but one, but still really good job.
Yeah.
You guys are smart.
You're just really good at moving your body.
Yeah, you're so good at expressing yourself.
Oh, really? Oh, that's sweet.
You don't have to put it that forth. Thank you.
All right, well you guys want a prize?
And the prize is a pose each.
You guys get to request one.
A special exclusive privilege.
A special privilege.
Let's start here with Zeta.
Can I request a somersault or a flip?
Oh, no, no, no. I can't do flips.
Can I request uh- What's your favorite number, Ame?
My favorite number? I like the number 6, 12, an even number.
A six?
Okay, uh 6 jumping jacks.
I should have picked two or one.
That's a punishment.
Okay, all right. I'll do the six poses.
Sorry, I had a hiccup.
Okay, I'm ready.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
like a full stretch, it's so cute
Yeah
Okay, six jumping jacks.
I need it. I need it, so.
My stamina's really bad.
My stamina is really bad.
Thank you. Thank you. Punishment?
Oh, I forgot to do the screenshot. Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Oh, you need one more? Is that what you're saying?
All right. All right.
You got it ready? Jumping jack? Yeah, yeah, yeah, I got I got this one.
You got it ready? Jumping jack? Yeah, yeah, I got this one.
Eeee-yah!
Hyah!
Okay!
You guys really dotted that, that was fast.
All right. Next, pose a minute.
Mmm, got it got it think about it.
Hmm, gotta gotta think about it.
How about you do the thinker pose again? I asked you to do it last year.
Oh, that's right. Yes. At the buffs and birthday.
Yes. Okay, uh I think I have to like kneel.
Oh wait, let me move over here a little bit.
Okay. Deep thought.
Oh, you're seeing it looks so cool. Oh, shit. Super cool.
Oh, your scene looks so cool. Oh, shit, it's super cool.
Thinking, thinking so hard. That would be perfect. Miss super deep thinking thinker.
Thinking, thinking so hard... That would be perfect. Miss super deep-thinking thinker.
Any for your thoughts, ma'am?
Um, You guys are cute, that's it. That's all I can think of right now.
I knew it. All right, uh next up Ollie's pose.
I knew it. All right, next up, Ollie's pose.
What would you like, ma'am?
Well, uh since it ask for jumping jacks, can I ask for a for a 20 seconds plank?
Well, since it asked for jumping jacks, can I ask for a 20-second plank?
A plank? Okay, not like a the one where you have to hold for your abs, but like the one
A plank? Okay, not like the one where you have to hold for your abs,
the meme one, right?
but like the meme one, right?
The me What does the meme one look like?
The me— What does the meme one look like?
It was like the the it was it was popular for a while. I'm going to plank here.
It was like the— it was popular for a while. Uh, I'm going to plank here.
Yeah, in random spots. The more random, the more it likes you got
Yeah, in random spots. The more random, the more it likes you,
Oh, I want to see it!
Oh, okay, okay. Yeah, yeah, it's just this one.
Wait, 20 seconds? Mentally and physically here.
Now do the worm! I look like a dead fish!
Has it been 20 seconds yet?
We just say it was 20 seconds.
Good enough.
Yay!
Okay. Thank you guys for the poses.
Thank you for doing them.
Oh, yeah.
Yes shaders.
All right. I'm so happy that you guys could be here with me. Thank you for coming. Thank you for your support.
That was so cute. All right. You're cute.
I'll see you guys again soon. Thank you.
All right, mata ne!
Thank you. Okay, bye-bye.
All right, next up we have uh let me check my bulletin board back there.
Uh, that's right.
It's kind of a bit messy cuz we had so many guests here and I haven't cleaned in a while.
It's kind of a bit messy 'cause we had so many guests here and I haven't cleaned in a while.
I got to get my vacuum cleaner. Yeah, that's right.
3D vacuum cleaner stream. Where is that vacuum cleaner?
What's all this? Buba!
Ah, there's my vacuum cleaner. There is.
Ah, there's my vacuum cleaner. There it is.
Right over there, Buba. Yeah, these streets are just incentives um for Buba to clean the room.
Right over there, Buba. Yeah, these treats are just incentives for Buba to clean the room.
I'm just getting these are actually all of your guys' super chats. I saw like a bunch of rainbow in the preview and the pre chat.
I'm just kidding, these are actually all of your guys' super chats. I saw like a bunch of rainbows in the preview and the pre-chat.
And uh yeah, I saw some may gifted memberships too. Thank you so much.
As you can see, all of these super chats go straight into Baba's belly. Baba. Wait Baba. Come back! Baba!
As you can see, all of these super chats go straight into Buba's belly. Buba, wait Buba. Come back! Buba!
There he goes! Go!
Um, so Buba's eating all of them. So thank you so much for all the support.
This uh this is a super chat, that one's a super chat. And that one's a super chat.
All right. Well, now we have some time while Buba cleans up all of these bones.
Now we have some time for pose requests and stuff. Yeah. Uh from you guys, from chat, cuz I can see the chat.
Now we have some time for pose requests and stuff, yeah, uh from you guys, from chat, 'cause I can see the chat.
And I wanted to know if there's anything that you guys want to see in 3D since I'm only here.
It's only possible because you guys made it possible. Yeah. All of your support over the last few years. Isn't that weird to say?
Splits?
Kamen on?
Oh, wait. What do you usually say to Kamen on?
Oh, you come around here often? I don't know.
Okay, okay. A cartwheel.
doesn't ask. I mean we have to compare, right?
We have to be able to compare.
Alright, hopefully I don't mess this up. I didn't do a cartwheel today.
Not even during rehearsal or anything.
I was like, I'm going to save it.
Okay. Wait, we got to warm up.
Yeah, we did it!
A cartwheel is just a side flip, okay?
Just so you guys know, it's like a sideways flip, pretty much.
I think.
Nice, nice.
Okay, okay. Any other requests you guys have for me? We have some time, so I think we're good.
Sorry, my nose is itchy.
The worm! I already did the worm!
My pants?
No, you guys have seen them enough times already.
Crab, okay, I can do crab.
A Jojo pose.
Um, I mean, uh, some random pose from some generic thing.
Wait, what do they usually do? Like this.
T-pose. Okay, okay.
Oh, T-pose.
I'm a helicopter.
Jack-o'-pose. Wait, how does that go again?
Is this right? Is something like this? I don't remember actually.
Something like that.
A ground pound.
I don't think I could do that on this floor.
I could do like a ground pound squat, kind of.
That seems close enough.
A bridge.
Oh, isn't that like where you go back? I don't know, I feel like I'm going to mess up something if I do that.
Oh, isn't that like where you go back? I feel like I'm going to mess up something if I do that.
Oh well.
They said no, no bridge.
Okay, something else?
How about why don't you guys pose? Because I'm sure your gamer posture is messed up. Posture check!
Gamer stretches, let's go.
Do you guys stretch today? Do you know how important stretching is?
For your limbs? You guys just sit and watch streams all day, you don't stretch.
Your neck's probably like, like that.
Okay. Check, posture check.
Oh yeah, I discovered this when we were practicing. Look.
Wait. What did I do?
I look like a bird.
Oh, I know you guys are going to ask, but this does not come off the cape always stays on, okay?
It always stays on.
The coat always stays on.
I look like a lizard.
Ow, my elbows cracked.
Feels nice.
Nerfed.
Uh, do you guys have any other poses for me? This is your last chance.
Last chance.
A dab.
Oh, of course! How can I forget?
Oh, of course! How could I forget?
I'll do a really epic one.
Did that work?
Not singing any song in particular.
I can't do a backflip, okay?
Maybe if I was on trampoline, I used to be able to do one on a...
Maybe if I was on a trampoline, I used to be able to do one on a...
We gotta get a trampoline here, staff, okay?
In my office, yes, I need a trampoline.
It has so many hidden features though. You guys probably don't even know.
Not yet, anyways.
Moonwalk. I can try.
I actually don't really know how to do it, how to moonwalk properly.
What is, can you guys, what is the griddy? Can you guys teach me? I feel like I've seen it, but maybe I just time traveled too much, you know?
Can you guys teach me the griddy? I feel like I've seen it, but maybe I just time traveled too much, you know?
I don't know it properly.
Wait, no, this is a... This is a sprinkler, like the shopping cart.
The macaroni.
Isn't, don't you do a slap during that?
I didn't sing anything, there was no song there.
Oh, idol step.
Wait, how do you do it again? Uh, I'm an idol. Skiing dance.
Wait, how do you do it again? I'm an idol. Skiing dance.
All right. Now, it's the last...
pose, what you'd do for the last one.
Skanking. Do you guys know what skanking is?
It's a specific dance where you go like this.
All right.
That was the last pose.
So I've been told.
All right.
Now it's time for... announcements!
I can't believe how fast the time went.
All right, let's go announce it! Yeah!
Oh, hey!
As you guys know, always at the end of these things, there's an announcement.
What could it be? I wonder.
Could it be something in this room? Like a really cool box or that cool vase over there that doesn't hold anything weird in it?
Or, yeah, I actually don't know.
Why don't we take a look at the image? Ta-da!
Private Investigator Cap.
Ame hat!
That's right, you too can become a detective!
It actually, this picture makes it look super like a hexagon, but it doesn't look like that when you wear it, okay?
It's very cool and round, and it looks just like my hat. It's really cool.
You guys, I want you to see it. So, you know, if you want to, you can get one, and it will be on sale tomorrow during all of Myth's item sales.
Yeah, it looks really, really cool, and it's adjustable in the back, and also the ribbon comes off.
So, you know, if you're a cool macho man and you don't want to be a cute anime girl, you can just put it up and it comes off.
Let me catch my breath. Ah, so much excitement!
And I still have something else in store. Something else soon.
About tasting, see ya. You can buy it now... uh, not now, tomorrow, it'll go on sale.
And I have a I have one, actually. I mean, obviously, I have one myself.
But I have one, and people have been trying it on and they're like, 'Oh my god, this is so cute.' Like, Iris tried it on, and Zeta tried it on, and Ena tried it on, and yeah, it's super cute.
So, if you guys are interested, you can buy it. Yeah, it's right here, you know. This is my model for today.
You can get you can this can be you. But you look way cooler wearing it, I promise. Okay, not I promise.
Yeah, we still have We still have some stuff left, huh? We still have some time left. A little bit of time. Shoo shoo, go away. Okay.
Yeah, so, um, oh yeah, I just wanted to thank you guys also. Make sure to check out our group collab stream tomorrow.
It will be live and we're all going to be there, all five of Myth, and we have some cool stuff to show you and it's going to be really, really fun. I'm actually really looking forward to it cause uh you know, just being together is really fun in general.
And yeah, I'm really happy. It's super weird that I got to be here um in Japan doing this, you know, where I am.
So it's super cool. I used to just be somebody that would do like uh, you know, really terrible, bad VR stuff, sometimes in public, even at an internet cafe once.
And now I get to do it in front of professional staff.
It's pretty crazy to think about, and I hope that one day, you know, even if you don't have the same experience that you guys get to experience something just as fulfilling.
Because I feel really happy to be here. And yeah, I'm not going to cry, I'm not going to cry.
Yeah, I'm super happy, so thank you, thank you for making it possible to be here. And um there is one last thing that I want to show you guys, okay?
And share my happiness with you a little bit too. Okay. Shall we see what it is?
Okay, I'm going now. What's this? Surprise? Surprise!
終わるわけない 終わらないよ
There's no way it'll end, it won't end.
目指すはどこ? ここはどこでしょう?
Where are we heading? Where even is this?
これから何が始まるのかな?
What's going to start from here on out?
気付けば君との旅支度
Before I knew it, we're packing for a journey.
モノクロに輝く楽園
A paradise shining in monochrome.
作りましょう 作りましょう あなたと私たちの世界をさ 作りましょう
Let's build it, let's build our world, you and I.
始めましょう 始めましょう 何から始めましょう
Let's start, let's start, where should we begin?
踊りましょう 踊りましょう 乗り乗りで踊りましょう
Let's dance, let's dance, let's dance along to the rhythm.
終末旅行が始まるぞふたり
Our girls' last tour is starting, the two of us.
ぽぱぽぱぽぱぱん
Pop a pop a pop a pan
目覚めた場所ここはどこでしょう？
Waking up, where could this place be?
これから何が始まるのかな？
What is going to start from now on?
気づけばキミとの旅支度
Before I realized, getting ready for a trip with you
モノクロに輝く楽園へ
To a paradise shining in monochrome
作りましょう 作りましょう
Let's make it, let's make it
あなたと世界のさぁ作りましょう
Let's make a world with you, come on
始めましょう 始めましょう
Let's start it, let's start it
なにかから始めましょう
Let's start with something
踊りましょう 踊りましょう
Let's dance, let's dance
ノリノリで踊りましょう
Let's dance with good vibes
終末旅行が始まるぞ
The end-of-the-world journey begins!
ふたりぼっちの世界は
The world of just the two of us
本日も回っている
Is spinning today as well
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after too
キミの隣にいられるかな？
Can I stay by your side?
お願い
Please
お腹空いた
I'm so hungry
食べ物おくれ
Give me food
甘いものガオー食べたいな
I want to eat something sweet
ふわりゆらゆら乗りこらりと
Swaying slowly, riding along
乗り切るべし今日もまた
We'll get through today as well
作りましょう 作りましょう
Let's make it, let's make it
あなたと世界のさぁ作りましょう
Let's make a world with you, come on
始めましょう 始めましょう
Let's start it, let's start it
なにかから始めましょう
Let's start with something
踊りましょう 踊りましょう
Let's dance, let's dance
ノリノリで踊りましょう
Let's dance with good vibes
終末旅行が始まるぞ
The end-of-the-world journey begins!
ふたりぼっちの未来が
The future of just the two of us
本日の課題である
Is today's assignment
大好きなキミといられれば
If I can be with my beloved you
不正解だって大正解
Even a wrong answer is the right answer
ふんわりもちもちのほっぺに
On your soft, fluffy cheeks
いつだって見とれてたいの
I always want to be gazing at them
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after too
ずっとそれに触れていたいたいから
I want to keep touching them forever
終末旅行が始まるぞ
Our final tour is starting!
ふたりぼっちの世界は
The world of just the two of us
本日も回っている
Is spinning today as well
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after too
キミの隣にいられるかな？
Can I stay by your side?
お願い
Please
もう終んない
More one night
ふたりぼっちの世界は
The world of just the two of us
本日も回っている
Is spinning today as well
今日も明日も明後日も
Today, tomorrow, and the day after too
キミの隣にいられるかな？
Can I stay by your side?
お願い
Please
もう終んない
More one night
ジャーニー
Journey!
Thank you for coming to my stream!
Stay tuned everyone, we'll be releasing our cover soon!
Bye bye!